Swetank Subham

Senior Software Engineer, Python

hone +91 9110 09 0019

Email swetanksubham.r@gmail.com

LinkedIn /in/swetank-subham/

Website https://swetanksubham.com/

Address Muzaffarpur, Bihar



With around **3 years** of experience in Software **Back-end Development** and **Management**, which includes several web-apps, scripts, APIs. I describe myself as a life-long learner, implementer and tech enthusiast. I prefer smart work but always ready for hard work if required.

Skills

Python	Shell Scripting		JavaScript	Pandas	Git	Jira	Linux	Docker		Data Structures	
HTML	CSS	OOP	Tesseract	Agile Meth	odology	PHP	My:	MySQL O _l		nCV	PySpark
RASA	Sanic JSON		Django								

Work History

RenewBuy, Gurgaon

30th May 2022 - Present

Senior Software Engineer

Working with team responsible for generating payouts and wallet systems. Developing APIs and backend optimisations, troubleshooting issues, code review, daily stand-up.

Knowlarity Communications Pvt. Ltd., Gurgaon

30th September 2021 – 29th May 2022 [8 months]

Software Developer

Worked on OBD (Outbound Calls). Role includes feature development, enhancement and possible optimisations, troubleshooting production issues, code review, daily stand-up and assistance during production activities.

Great Software Laboratory Pvt. Ltd., Pune

2nd July 2019 – 29th September 2021 [2 year 3 months]

Software Engineer

Worked on multiple projects. Role includes architecture design for new projects, feature development, enhancement and possible optimisations, troubleshooting production issues, code review, daily stand-up and assistance during production activities.

Great Software Laboratory Pvt. Ltd., Pune

2nd August 2018 – 30th June 2019 [11 months]

Software Engineer (Intern)

Worked as a full-stack developer. Role includes feature development. Enhancement and possible optimisations, daily stand-up.

Education

Bachelor of Technology, Computer Science and Engineering

2015 - 2019

Lovely Professional University, Punjab

Certifications

Data Structures and Algorithms, Nano Degree, Udacity

ID: CANUTXDS

Link: https://graduation.udacity.com/confirm/CANUTXDS

The Complete 2022 Web Development Course - Build 15 Projects, Udemy

ID: UC-30HPQA6I

Link: https://www.udemy.com/certificate/UC-30HPQA6I/

Hobbies

- Playing Cricket
- Learning new technology
- Listening to music